Mo Zhai

1014 whirlaway ave Naperville IL 60540

Phone: (773)678-3620 Web: <u>www.zhaimobile.com</u> E-mail: mozhai@live.com

Me

I am an experienced software engineer with 3 years of professional experience. My experience covers development using Objective C, Java, .NET, C++, Javascript, Php, and many other languages on top of most popular frameworks. I have delivered several enterprise web applications as well as mobile apps for business in both iOS App Store and Android Play Store. I am a hard worker with great learning skills.

Skills

- Frameworks: iOS, Android, Liferay, ASP.Net MVC, J2EE, Lucene.Net, Drupal, OpenGL
- Language: Objective C, Java, JavaScript, C++, C#, Python, Php, R, SQL
- IDE and Tools: Visual Studio, Xcode, Eclipse, Git, JIRA, Unity3D, Bzr, and etc.
- Platforms: MacOS X, Windows, Linux

Experience

Full Stack Software Engineer @ Echelon Consulting, L.L.C.

5/2012 - now

- Developing core financial web applications for global business using ASP.Net MVC.
- Implemented iOS and Android apps (front-end and back-end) for A large law firm with more than 1,800 employees in 19 offices worldwide.
- Built auto-translation, searching, payment system, and analysis visualization tools for top business.
- Upgraded the company web site for a global management consulting firm using Liferay.

Software developer internships@ Space to Play

2/2012 - 4/2012

 Accomplished a 3Ds Max plug-in in C++, which facilitates editing and visualization of urban 3D building models from geo-spatial database (PostGIS).

Graduate Assistant and Tech support @ CDM, DePaul University

01/2011 - 03/2012

- Maintained and managed network, server and other equipments for labs.
- Operated software deployment and testing for classes and events.

Network Engineer @ China TieTong- Equipment Center

08/2007 - 03/2009

- Analyzed, and refined the central node of the company PSTN network.
- Analytics tool development for a multiple million equipment upgrading project.

Education

University of Chicago

Master of Science in **Analytics**, Master Candidate

DePaul University

Graduation March, 2012

Master of Science in Computer Game Development, GPA=3.98

Tianjin Normal University

Graduation July, 2007

Bachelor of Engineering in Compute Engineering, emphasis on **Information Engineering** GPA=**3.42** First rank scholarship